<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Assignment_1</string>
    <string name="copyright">"All images copyright GlenShaw.ca and Wikipedia for the fact's."</string>
    <string name="birds">Birds</string>
    <string name="Reptiles">Reptiles</string>
    <string name="Mammal">Mammal</string>
    <string name="Flora">Flora</string>
    <string name="Last">Last</string>
    <string name="Random">Random</string>
    <string name="developerName">Glen Shaw</string>
    <string name="counter">Counter</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="index">Index</string>
    <string name="nothingSaved">Nothing saved.</string>
    <string name="birdsString1">A bizarre wading bird of the southern coasts, the https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roseate_spoonbill uses its odd bill to strain small food items out of the water. </string>
    <string name="birdsString2">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_goldfinch (Spinus tristis), also known as the eastern goldfinch or "lightning bird," is a small North American bird in the finch family. It is migratory, ranging from mid-Alberta to North Carolina during the breeding season, and from just south of the Canada–United States border to Mexico during the winter.</string>
    <string name="birdsString3">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brown_pelican is a comically elegant bird with an oversized bill, sinuous neck, and big, dark body.</string>
    <string name="birdsString4">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cuban_emerald is a species of hummingbird in the Trochilidae family. It is found in a wide range of semi-open habitats in Cuba and the western Bahamas.</string>
    <string name="birdsString5">Also known as https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zapata_sparrow , an arguably more appropriate but far less evocative name, this species is the sole member of a genus endemic to Cuba.</string>
    <string name="reptileString1">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Allison%27s_anole (Anolis allisoni), also known as the blue-headed anole, is a species of anole. This lizard is found in Cuba (except the west and the far southeast), the Bay Islands and Cayos Cochinos off the mainland of Honduras, and Half Moon Caye off the mainland of Belize. There is also a single doubtful record from Cozumel, Mexico. This diurnal species is commonly seen on palm trunks and it feeds on invertebrates.</string>
    <string name="reptileString2">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Green_iguana (Iguana iguana), also known as the American iguana, is a large, arboreal, mostly herbivorous species of lizard of the genus Iguana. It is native to Central, South America, and the Caribbean. Usually, this animal is simply called the iguana. The green iguana ranges over a large geographic area, from southern Brazil and Paraguay as far north as Mexico and the Caribbean Islands. </string>
    <string name="reptileString3">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red-footed_tortoise (Chelonoidis carbonaria) is a species of tortoises from northern South America. These medium-sized tortoises generally average 30 cm (12 in) as adults, but can reach over 40 cm (16 in). They have dark-colored, loaf-shaped carapaces (back shell) with a lighter patch in the middle of each scute (scales on the shell), and dark limbs with brightly colored scales that range from pale yellow to dark red. Recognized differences are seen between red-footed tortoises from different regions.</string>
    <string name="reptileString4">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cyclura_nubila (Cyclura nubila), also known as the Cuban ground iguana or Cuban iguana,[3] is a species of lizard of the iguana family. It is the largest of the West Indian rock iguanas (genus Cyclura), one of the most endangered groups of lizards. This herbivorous species with red eyes, a thick tail, and spiked jowls is one of the largest lizards in the Caribbean.</string>
    <string name="reptileString5">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cuban_crocodile (Crocodylus rhombifer) is a small species of crocodile found only in Cuba. Typical length is 2.1–2.3 m (6.9–7.5 ft) and typical weight 70–80 kg (150–180 lb). Large males can reach as much as 3.5 m (11 ft) in length and weigh more than 215 kg (474 lb). Despite its modest size, it is a highly aggressive animal, and potentially dangerous to humans.</string>
    <string name="mammalString1">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mandrill (Mandrillus sphinx) is a primate of the Old World monkey (Cercopithecidae) family. It is one of two species assigned to the genus Mandrillus, along with the drill. Both the mandrill and the drill were once classified as baboons in the genus Papio, but they now have their own genus, Mandrillus. Although they look superficially like baboons, they are more closely related to Cerocebus mangabeys. Mandrills are found in southern Cameroon, Gabon, Equatorial Guinea, and Congo.</string>
    <string name="mammalString2">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gray_wolf or grey wolf (Canis lupus), also known as the timber wolf or western wolf, is a canine native to the wilderness and remote areas of Eurasia and North America. It is the largest extant member of its family, with males averaging 43–45 kg (95–99 lb), and females 36–38.5 kg (79–85 lb). Like the red wolf, it is distinguished from other Canis species by its larger size and less pointed features, particularly on the ears and muzzle.</string>
    <string name="mammalString3">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tiger (Panthera tigris) is the largest cat species, most recognisable for their pattern of dark vertical stripes on reddish-orange fur with a lighter underside. The species is classified in the genus Panthera with the lion, leopard, jaguar and snow leopard.</string>
    <string name="mammalString4">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_black_bear (Ursus americanus) is a medium-sized bear native to North America. It is the continent s smallest and most widely distributed bear species. Black bears are omnivores with their diets varying greatly depending on season and location.</string>
    <string name="mammalString5">The https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red_fox (Vulpes vulpes), largest of the true foxes, has the greatest geographic range of all members of the Carnivora family, being present across the entire Northern Hemisphere from the Arctic Circle to North Africa, North America and Eurasia. It is listed as least concern by the IUCN.</string>
    <string name="floraString1">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Allamanda_cathartica , commonly called golden trumpet, common trumpetvine, and yellow allamanda, is a species of flowering plant of the genus Allamanda in the family Apocynaceae. It is native to Brazil. This plant is cited in Flora Brasiliensis by Carl Friedrich Philipp von Martius.</string>
    <string name="floraString2">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nymphaeaceae is a family of flowering plants, commonly called water lilies. They live as rhizomatous aquatic herbs in temperate and tropical climates around the world. The family contains five genera with about 70 known species. Water lilies are rooted in soil in bodies of water, with leaves and flowers floating on or emergent from the surface. </string>
    <string name="floraString3">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Convolvulus is a genus of about 200 to 250 species of flowering plants in the bindweed family Convolvulaceae, with a cosmopolitan distribution. Common names include bindweed and morning glory, both names shared with other closely related genera.</string>
    <string name="floraString4">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zinnia is a genus of plants of the sunflower tribe within the daisy family. They are native to scrub and dry grassland in an area stretching from the Southwestern United States to South America, with a centre of diversity in Mexico.</string>
    <string name="floraString5">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hibiscus is a genus of flowering plants in the mallow family, Malvaceae. The genus is quite large, comprising several hundred species that are native to warm-temperate, subtropical and tropical regions throughout the world. </string>
</resources>
